Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1
- Box: 40, Folder: 15 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Item 36: Notes and Quotes Index, Publication (Box 40, Folder 15)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance Company. January through December 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Notes and Quotes Index, Publication (Box 40, Folder 15)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance Company. January through December 1973. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 40, Folder 15)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance Company. no.275 (1962:Apr.). Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 40, Folder 15)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance Company. 25th Anniversary Issue. Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 40, Folder 15)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance Company. no.296 (1964:Jan.). Item is in English.
  - Item 41: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 40, Folder 15)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance Company. no.297 (1964:Feb.). Item is in English.
  - Item 42: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 40, Folder 15)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance Company. no.298 (1964:Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 43: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 40, Folder 15)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance Company. no.299 (1964:Apr.). Item is in English.
  - Item 44: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 40, Folder 15)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance Company. no.300 (1964:May). Item is in English.
  - Item 45: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 40, Folder 15)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance Company. no.301 (1964:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 46: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 40, Folder 15)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance Company. no.302 (1964:July). Item is in English.
  - Item 47: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 40, Folder 15)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance Company. no.303 (1964:Aug.). Item is in English.
  - Item 48: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 40, Folder 15)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance Company. no.304 (1964:Sep.). Item is in English.
  - Item 49: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 40, Folder 15)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance Company. no.305 (1964:Oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 50: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 40, Folder 15)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance Company. no.306 (1964:Nov.). Item is in English.
  - Item 51: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 40, Folder 15)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance Company. no.307 (1964:Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 52: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 40, Folder 15)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance Company. no.332 (1967:Jan.). Item is in English.
  - Item 53: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 40, Folder 15)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance Company. no.332 (1967:Jan.). Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 54: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 40, Folder 15)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance Company. no.333 (1967:Feb.). Item is in English.
  - Item 55: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 40, Folder 15)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance Company. no.334 (1967:Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 56: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 40, Folder 15)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance Company. no.334 (1967:Mar.) Should be no.335 (1967:Apr.). Item is in English.
  - Item 57: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 40, Folder 15)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance Company. no.336 (1967:May). Item is in English.
- Box: 40, Folder: 16 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Is There a Job Waiting for a Friend?, Publication (Box 40, Folder 16)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Connecticut General, Publication (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: You and Connecticut General, Publication (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: Principles and Objectives, Publication (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Item 5: You and Connecticut General, Publication (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Item 6: Actuary at Connecticut General, Publication (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Item 7: Connecticut General, Publication (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Item 8: The Group Sales Representative with Connecticut General, Publication (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Item 9: Women at Connecticut General Life Insurance, Publication (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Item 10: You and Connecticut General Life Insurance, Publication (Box 40, Folder 16)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: College Level Recruiting Program, Publication (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Item 12: 1958 Management Recruiting Program, Publication (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Item 13: For You Who Want More Than "Just a Job", Publication (Box 40, Folder 16)
- Box: 40, Folder: 17 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Supervisor's Manual: Personnel Policy and Procedure, Publication (Box 40, Folder 17)
- Box: 41, Folder: 1 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Life in General, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.86 (1959:Spring/Summer). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Life in General, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.176 (1961:Feb. 27). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Life in General, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.290 (1963:May 6). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Life in General, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.291 (1963:May 13). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Life in General, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.292 (1963:May 20). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Life in General, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.293 (1963:May 27). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Life in General, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.294 (1963:June 3). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Focus, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.28 (1963:May 13). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: A Place to Begin, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: A Place to Begin, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: You and Connecticut General, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: You and Connecticut General, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Workshop Preview, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Commerce and Industry Association Institute. September/December 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Nation's Leaders Stay a Step Ahead With Connecticut General Group Benefits, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: Empolyer Information Sheet, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.150 (1951:Nov.). Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.152 (1952:Jan.). Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.153 (1952:Feb.). Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.154 (1952:Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.155 (1952:Apr.). Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.156 (1952:May). Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.157 (1952:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.158 (1952:July). Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.159 (1952:Aug.). Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.160 (1952:Sep.). Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.161 (1952:Oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.162 (1952:Nov.). Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.163 (1952:Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.164 (1953:Jan.). Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.165 (1953:Feb.). Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.166 (1953:Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.167 (1953:Apr.). Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.168 (1953:May). Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.169 (1953:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.171 (1953:Aug.). Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.172 (1953:Sep.). Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.174 (1953:Nov.). Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.175 (1953:Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.176 (1954:Jan.). Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.177 (1954:Feb.). Item is in English.
  - Item 41: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.178 (1954:Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 42: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.179 (1954:Apr.). Item is in English.
  - Item 43: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.180 (1954:May). Item is in English.
  - Item 44: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.181 (1954:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 45: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.182 (1954:July). Item is in English.
  - Item 46: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.183 (1954:Aug.). Item is in English.
  - Item 47: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.184 (1954:Sep.). Item is in English.
  - Item 48: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.185 (1954:Oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 49: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.186 (1954:Nov.). Item is in English.
  - Item 50: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.187 (1954:Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 51: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.188 (1955:Jan.). Item is in English.
  - Item 52: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.189 (1955:Feb.). Item is in English.
  - Item 53: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.190 (1955:Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 54: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.191 (1955:Apr.). Item is in English.
  - Item 55: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.192 (1955:May). Item is in English.
  - Item 56: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.193 (1955:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 57: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.194 (1955:July). Item is in English.
  - Item 58: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.195 (1955:Aug.). Item is in English.
  - Item 59: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.196 (1955:Sep.). Item is in English.
  - Item 60: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.198 (1955:Nov.). Item is in English.
  - Item 61: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.199 (1955:Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 62: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.200 (1956:Jan.). Item is in English.
  - Item 63: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.201 (1956:Feb.). Item is in English.
  - Item 64: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.202 (1956:Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 65: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.203 (1956:Apr.). Item is in English.
  - Item 66: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.204 (1956:May). Item is in English.
  - Item 67: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.205 (1956:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 68: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.206 (1956:July). Item is in English.
  - Item 69: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.207 (1956:Aug.). Item is in English.
  - Item 70: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.208 (1956:Sep.). Item is in English.
  - Item 71: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.209 (1956:Oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 72: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.210 (1956:Nov.). Item is in English.
  - Item 73: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.211 (1956:Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 74: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.212 (1957:Jan.). Item is in English.
  - Item 75: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.213 (1957:Feb.). Item is in English.
  - Item 76: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.214 (1957:Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 77: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.215 (1957:Apr.). Item is in English.
  - Item 78: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.216 (1957:May). Item is in English.
  - Item 79: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.217 (1957:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 80: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.218 (1957:July). Item is in English.
  - Item 81: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.219 (1957:Aug.). Item is in English.
  - Item 82: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.220 (1957:Sep.). Item is in English.
  - Item 83: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.221 (1957:Oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 84: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.222 (1957:Nov.). Item is in English.
  - Item 85: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.223 (1957:Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 86: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.224 (1958:Jan.). Item is in English.
  - Item 87: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.225 (1958:Feb.). Item is in English.
  - Item 88: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.226 (1958:Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 89: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.227 (1958:Apr.). Item is in English.
  - Item 90: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.228 (1958:May). Item is in English.
  - Item 91: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.229 (1958:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 92: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.230 (1958:July). Item is in English.
  - Item 93: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.231 (1958:Aug.). Item is in English.
  - Item 94: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.232 (1958:Sep.). Item is in English.
  - Item 95: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.233 (1958:Oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 96: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.234 (1958:Nov.). Item is in English.
  - Item 97: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.235 (1958:Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 98: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.236 (1959:Jan.). Item is in English.
  - Item 99: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.237 (1959:Feb.). Item is in English.
  - Item 100: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.238 (1959:Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 101: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.239 (1959:Apr.). Item is in English.
  - Item 102: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.240 (1959:May). Item is in English.
  - Item 103: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.241 (1959:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 104: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.242 (1959:July). Item is in English.
  - Item 105: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.243 (1959:Aug.). Item is in English.
  - Item 106: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.244 (1959:Sep.). Item is in English.
  - Item 107: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.245 (1959:Oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 108: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.246 (1959:Nov.). Item is in English.
  - Item 109: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.247 (1959:Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 110: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.248 (1960:Jan.). Item is in English.
  - Item 111: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.249 (1960:Feb.). Item is in English.
  - Item 112: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.250 (1960:Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 113: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.251 (1960:Apr.). Item is in English.
  - Item 114: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.252 (1960:May). Item is in English.
  - Item 115: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.253 (1960:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 116: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.254 (1960:July). Item is in English.
  - Item 117: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.255 (1960:Aug.). Item is in English.
  - Item 118: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.256 (1960:Sep.). Item is in English.
  - Item 119: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.257 (1960:Oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 120: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.258 (1960:Nov.). Item is in English.
  - Item 121: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.259 (1960:Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 122: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.260 (1961:Jan.). Item is in English.
  - Item 123: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.261 (1961:Feb.). Item is in English.
  - Item 124: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.262 (1961:Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 125: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.263 (1961:Apr.). Item is in English.
  - Item 126: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.264 (1961:May). Item is in English.
  - Item 127: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.265 (1961:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 128: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.266 (1961:July). Item is in English.
  - Item 129: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.267 (1961:Aug.). Item is in English.
  - Item 130: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.268 (1961:Sep.). Item is in English.
  - Item 131: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.269 (1961:OCt.). Item is in English.
  - Item 132: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.270 (1961:Nov.). Item is in English.
  - Item 133: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By Connecticut General Life Insurance. no.271 (1961:Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 134: Notes and Quotes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)